(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
ねね～ちらい～ぶ ４年目もよろしくね！
Nene-chi Live! Please support me in my 4th year too!
ゲストいっぱいでお祝い！
Celebrating with lots of guests!
#桃鈴ねねの４年目
#MomosuzuNene4thYear
モモノネ
作詞・作曲・編曲：ヒゲドライバー
Momonone
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hige Driver
いくつもの　夢という花が
Several flowers called dreams
この惑星(ほし)　には咲いていたんだ
Were blooming on this planet
自分も　手にとって憧れては
I too, picked them up and yearned for them
思い切り　羽を広げたんだ
And spread my wings as wide as I could
みんな見えるかー？
Can everyone see me?
そう　不安な時も
Yes, even in uneasy times
あ、あ、みんなバイバイ！ちょっと待って、やり直し！ごめんねー！
Ah, ah, bye-bye everyone! Wait a second, redo! Sorry!
あー、みんなー！あ、いいえ、みんな何も見てなかった、いいね？
Ah, everyone! Ah, no, everyone saw nothing, okay?
もう一回、最初から、始めよう！
One more time, from the beginning, let's start!
イエーイ！
Yay!
あ、今度こそねねがどこにいるかわかりましたかー？
Ah, this time, did you find where Nene is?
わー！見える見える！
Wow! I see you, I see you!
いくつもの　夢という花が
Several flowers called dreams
この惑星(ほし)　には咲いていたんだ
Were blooming on this planet
自分も　手にとって憧れては
I too, picked them up and yearned for them
思い切り　羽を広げたんだ
And spread my wings as wide as I could
そう　不安な時も
Yes, even in uneasy times
いつも支えてくれてるねっこ
The Nekko who are always supporting me
だからきっと　もっと大きくなれる
So surely, I can grow even bigger
思いはまっすぐ　伸びていけ
May my thoughts stretch out straight
あの空に　届くように
To reach that sky
モモノネ　なんて...
Momonone is...
...ない 目いっぱい
...not, as hard as I can,
咲かせるよ
I'll make it bloom.
自分という名の大きな花
A great flower called myself,
満開のモモノネ
the Momonone in full bloom.
よいしょー！みんなー！
Heave-ho! Everyone!
おうちにプレゼントが届いてる人、
If a present has arrived at your home,
開けてください！
please open it!
おりゃあー！
Oryaa!
食らえ！ねねの...
Take this! Nene's...
何が入ってるかと言うと...
As for what's inside...
ねねのサインボール砲だ！
it's Nene's signed ball cannon!
おら食らえ！
Take that!
おらおらおらおらおら！みんな、飛ぶぞー！
Ora ora ora ora ora! Everyone, we're taking flight!
うをぉぉぉー！おらおらおらおらおら！
Uwoooo! Take that, take that, take that!
すごい量が出るんだから！
Because a huge amount is coming out!
おら！下の人もおら！
Hey! You people below too!
真下の人も食らえ！
The people right underneath, take this too!
直下で！うをぉぉぉー！
Direct hit! Uwoooo!
思いは太陽の光浴びて
Thoughts bask in the sunlight,
鮮やかに輝くよ 空を全部
and shine brightly, across the whole sky.
おおーおーおーおー
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
目いっぱいこの両手広げてさ
Spread these hands as wide as you can.
ありがとみんな！開けてくれたかな？
Thank you, everyone! Did you open it?
ツイッターとかよかったら載せて見せてね！
If you'd like, post it on Twitter and show me!
おいえ！
Oh yeah!
はっ！
Ha!
あぶなーい！
That was close!
みんながいれば何でもできるよ
With all of you, I can do anything.
思いのまま すぐの道
A straight path as my heart desires.
で行け あの空に届くように
Go, so that you reach that sky.
もう怖いものなんてない
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore.
目いっぱい咲かせるよ みんなで咲かそう
I'll make it bloom; let's all make it bloom together.
たくさんの花
So many flowers.
満開のモモノネ
The Momonone in full bloom.
みんな見て！なに？
Everyone, look! What is it?
ねねは何に一体乗ってるんだ？
What on earth is Nene riding?
これはなんだなんだー？
What is this, what is this?
うわ！あ！地面が！地面が来るー！
Whoa! Ah! The ground! The ground is coming!
花の塔
Flower Tower
作詞・作曲：さユり 編曲：名越由貴也 (MUSIC FOR MUSIC)
Lyrics/Composition: Sayuri / Arrangement: Yukiya Nagoshi (MUSIC FOR MUSIC)
君が持ってきた漫画
The manga you brought,
くれた知らない名前の花
the flowers you gave me with names I didn't know.
今日はまだ来ないかな
I wonder if you're not coming yet today;
初めての感情知ってしまった
I've learned a new feeling for the first time.
窓に飾った笑顔なぞって
Tracing the smile I decorated on the window,
一人で宇宙を旅して
I travel through space alone.
それだけでいいはずだったのに
That should have been enough, but...
君の手を握ってしまったら
Now that I've taken your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this city that knows no loneliness...
もう二度と帰って来ることはできない
I can never return again,
色化粧
with this make-up of colors.
君が手を差し伸べた光で 影が生まれる
With the light you reached out with, a shadow is born.
歌って聞かせて
Sing it to me, let me hear
この話の続き
the rest of this story,
連れて行って見たことない星まで
take me to a star I've never seen before.
誰にも声も届かない
Atop the tower where no one's voice reaches,
高くそびえ立った塔の上
the tower that towers so high.
飛ばす風船葛
I release the balloon vines;
僕は君に笑ってほしいんだ
I want you to smile.
満たされない穴を...
The holes that cannot be filled...
...差し出した拳で
...With my outstretched fist,
これまでは埋めてきたけど
I've filled it in until now, but
退屈な日々を蹴散らして
Kicking away the boring days,
君と二人でこの街中を
just the two of us, throughout this city,
泳げたらそれはどれだけ素敵なことでしょう
if we could swim, how wonderful that would be.
出したことないほど大きな声で
With a voice louder than ever before,
誘う君に伝わる
I'll call out to you, and it will reach you.
歪なくらいがさきっとちょうどいいね
A bit of distortion is probably just right,
世界の端と端を結んで
tying together the ends of the world.
窓に描いちゃった温かい顔なぞって
Tracing the warm face I drew on the window,
一人で宇宙を旅して
traveling through space alone.
それだけでも不自由はないけど
Even with just that, I have no complaints, but
僕は選んでみたいのだ
I want to try choosing this—
高鳴る心 謎だらけの空を
my throbbing heart and the sky full of mysteries.
安全なループを今書き換えて
Now, rewriting the safe loop.
君の手を握ってしまったら
If I were to take your hand,
孤独を知らないこの街には
to this city that knows no loneliness,
もう二度と帰って来ることはできないのでしょう
we probably wouldn't ever be able to return.
いくらでも迷いの中から
From within any amount of hesitation,
光も影も見に行こう
let's go see both the light and the shadows.
歌って聴かせてこの話の続き
Sing to me, and tell me the rest of this story.
連れて行って見たことない星まで
Take me to a star I've never seen before.
世界の端と端を結んで
Tying together the ends of the world.
はーい！というわけで、こんねね！
Hi! And so, Kon-Nene!
ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当、
Hololive 5th Gen, orange member,
みんなの心の、エナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねでーす！
everyone's heart's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene here!
皆さん、ねね～ちらいぶ4年目へようこそー！
Everyone, welcome to Nene-chiraibu 4th year!
みんな見て！今日ステージがこれ初お披露目になりまーす！
Everyone look! This stage is making its debut today!
見て！青い空に、えっと、木と、あとフェンスと、
Look! In the blue sky... uh, trees, and fences...
あと、うんと、蝶々と、えっと、虫。すごーい！
and, um, butterflies and... uh, bugs. Amazing!
で、風船、ねねの風船と、ねこまーまんさんの風船といっぱいありまーす！
And balloons, Nene's balloons and Nekomanma balloons, there's so many!
そして、桃鈴ねねの2番のところで
And, during the second part of Momosuzunene,
みんなに、えっと、初お披露目したバズーカ砲！
I debuted the bazooka cannon for everyone!
みんなにサインボール、キャッチできた人はいましたでしょうか？
Did anyone catch a signed ball?
何人かのうちの人にはきっとね、
I'm sure some of you...
あのバーチャル越しにバーン！とこうボールが飛んできて
...caught a ball that flew through the virtual world with a "Bang!"
キャッチできたんじゃないかなとは思いまーす！
I think you were able to catch it!
さあ、今日のタグなんですけど、
Now, about today's hashtag,
今日は #桃鈴ねねの4周年 、
it's #MomosuzuNeneNo4thAnniversary,
これでいきたいと思いますので、
I'd like to go with this, so...
サインボール捕まえた人も、
whether you caught a signed ball
可愛いねねがね、いっぱい撮れた人も、
or took lots of pictures of cute Nene,
いっぱいツイートしてくれると嬉しいでーす！
I'd be happy if you tweeted a lot!
さあ、今回のライブは、可愛いねね、
Now, this live performance features cute Nene,
かっこいいねね、うーんセクシーなねねが、いっぱい...
cool Nene, and sexy Nene...
あ、やめて！やめてください！
Ah, stop it! Please stop!
あ、いっぱい見られる仕様となっておりまーす！
Ah, it's designed so you can see a lot!
というわけで、色々なゲストの方にも
So, since we have various guests
来ていただいていますので、
coming as well,
ハッシュタグつけていっぱいお写真撮って共有してください！
please use the hashtag, take lots of photos, and share them!
というわけで、早速ゲストパート行ってみたいと思いまーす！
And so, let's head straight to the guest part!
えいえいおー！
Ei Ei Oh!
Sky High! 羽ばたいて 最上よりも高く
Sky High! Fluttering higher than the highest point
最高！広がる世界へと
The best! To the expanding world!
Wow! プリキュア!
Wow! Precure!
雨上がりに虹のプリズム
A rainbow prism after the rain
何かが始まる空の気配
Signs in the sky that something is beginning
(空の気配)
(Signs in the sky)
確かめるように手を伸ばせば
If I reach out my hand as if to make sure
希望という光掴んでた 秒でキャッチ
I was grabbing the light called hope, catching it in a second
絶望を超えて 私たちは強くなる
Going beyond despair, we become stronger
涙を拭いて
Wipe away your tears
Fly High!
Take Off!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高潮の心意気
Flapping wings high in the sky, the height of spirit
イライラもキラキラにチェンジして
Changing even irritation into sparkle
未知の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
The unknown world, the future map is full of possibilities
同じ空 繋がる仲間
Friends connected under the same sky
明日へ続く奇跡
The miracle that continues to tomorrow
ひろがるスカイ！プリキュア
Hirogaru Sky! Precure
Wow!
つらいときは泣いてもいいよ
It's okay to cry when it's hard
何が起きたって見捨てない
No matter what happens, I won't abandon you
(だって見捨てない)
(Because I won't abandon you)
見上げる空は青く眩しい
The sky I look up to is blue and dazzling
明日こそはとまた頑張れる Never Mind
I can try hard again tomorrow, saying "never mind"
でこぼこ道でも歩く意味はきっとある
There's surely a meaning to walking even a bumpy road
転んだ後は
After falling down
Stand Up!
Jump Up!
天高く羽ばたいて 最高潮の心持ち
Flapping wings high in the sky, the height of feelings
ぬかるみもピカピカにチェンジして
Changing even the mud into shine
未完成で未確認の未来は自分次第
The incomplete and unconfirmed future depends on me
今ここに残す足跡
The footprints I leave here now
明日へ続く奇跡
The miracle that continues to tomorrow
ひろがるスカイ！プリキュア
Hirogaru Sky! Precure
「ありがとう」と言葉 優しさを繋ぐバトン
"Thank you" are words, a baton connecting kindness
次から次へと手渡しで届けたい
I want to deliver it by hand from one to the next
小さいことから始まる幸せの
Happiness starting from small things
輪を
The circle...
果てしなくとめどなく押し寄せるいつだって
Endlessly and ceaselessly, it's always surging
ぎくしゃくもワクワクにチェンジして
Changing even the awkwardness into excitement
天高く羽ばたいて 最高潮の心意気
Flapping wings high in the sky, the height of spirit
イライラもキラキラにチェンジして
Changing even irritation into sparkle
未知の世界 未来図は可能性でいっぱい
The unknown world, the future map is full of possibilities
同じ空 繋がる仲間
Friends connected under the same sky
明日へ続く奇跡
The miracle that continues to tomorrow
ひろがるスカイ！
Hirogaru Sky!
プリキュア
Precure
Wow!
(Uu! Nyaa! Uu! Nyaa! 世界は dark!)
(Uu! Nyaa! Uu! Nyaa! The world is dark!)
(Uu! Nyaa! Uu! Nyaa! Uu! Nyaa! Let's Nyaa!)
ココロねるねる 異教の神々
Heart is kneading, pagan gods
私もあなたも怖がりのもの好き
Both I and you are fearful curious people
ムリムリムリムリ 異教に逃げれば
Impossible, impossible... if you flee to a foreign land
私とあなたは縁で結ばれて
You and I are tied by fate
退屈に燃えよ 焼けるぞ溶けるぞ
Burn in boredom, it'll burn, it'll melt
生き物じゃない！
It's not a living thing!
視線ひやひや それでも好きです
Glance is chilling, but I still like it
私がいちばん欲しいのは太陽よ
What I want most is the Sun
姿ぱやぱや それでは行きましょう
Form is fuzzy, so let's go
私にいちばん似合うのは太陽よ
What suits me best is the Sun
(うー！にゃー！)
(Uhh! Nyaa!)
閑散耳は
Quiet ears are...
(うー！にゃー！)
(Uhh! Nyaa!)
何だんだい？
What is it?
(うー！にゃー！)
(Uhh! Nyaa!)
欲求不満は言葉にしなくちゃ
Frustration must be put into words
ほら嫌、うれしょ (にゃー！)
See, I hate it, but I'm happy (Nyaa!)
太陽なんか眩しくて
The sun is just so bright
闇の方が無限で (ドキドキ)
The darkness is infinite (Thump-thump)
太陽ばっか眩しくて
It's nothing but the bright sun
闇の方が素敵 (にゃー！)
The darkness is more wonderful (Nyaa!)
Chaos! Chaos! I wanna Chaos!
燃えよ混沌 無敵 (ドキドキ)
Burn on, Chaos, invincible (Thump-thump)
Chaos! Chaos! 歌せら Chaos!
Chaos! Chaos! Make us sing, Chaos!
燃えるような気持ち (おー！)
This burning feeling (Ohh!)
我々！遣れ遣れ！世界は…！
We are! Do it, do it! The world is...!
(うー！にゃー！うー！にゃー！)
(Uhh! Nyaa! Uhh! Nyaa!)
枕ポカポカ 無謀な神々
Warm pillows, reckless gods
私とあなたと僕だけは違うの
Only me, you, and I are different
絆のガブムリヤリ去れがち
The bonds tend to be torn away
私があなたを守るけどピンチ
I'll protect you, but we're in a pinch
可笑しいな 逃げるぞ蠢くぞ
That's strange, let's flee, they're squirming
(何終わってる？)
(What's over?)
ドッパリオリオリアリ ここまで来ました
I've come all the way here
私は黙って敵たちを蹴散らす
I'll silently kick the enemies away
不燃メラメラ ここではダメです
Non-flammable burning, this is no good
私に黙ってスカートはしないで
Don't hide your skirt from me
望むなら (全・全・全滅)
If you wish (To-To-Total Annihilation)
しましょうね (敵なんだやれやれ)
Let's do it (Good grief, they're enemies)
願わくば跡形もなくで
Hopefully, without a trace
あら、いらないでしょ (にゃー！)
Oh, you don't need it, right? (Nyaa!)
現在何と危険だった
How dangerous it was just now
光をもおください (ピカピカ)
Please give me light too (Sparkle)
現在何と危険だった
How dangerous it was just now
光もんで刺激 (おー！)
Stimulated by the light (Ohh!)
Madness! Madness! You want a madness!
読めば暴騰過激 (ドキドキ)
Radical if you read it (Thump-thump)
Madness! Madness! I'm annoying madness!
読めばきっとおしまい (おー！)
It's surely the end if you read it (Ohh!)
這い寄る！混沌！遣るらとほ！
Creeping! Chaos! Nyarlathotep!
太陽なんか眩しくて
The sun is just so bright
闇の方が無限で (ドキドキ)
The darkness is infinite (Thump-thump)
太陽ばっか眩しくて
It's nothing but the bright sun
闇の方が素敵 (にゃー！)
The darkness is more wonderful (Nyaa!)
Chaos! Chaos! I wanna Chaos!
燃えよ混沌 無敵 (ドキドキ)
Burn on, Chaos, invincible (Thump-thump)
Chaos! Chaos! 歌せら Chaos!
Chaos! Chaos! Make us sing, Chaos!
燃えるような気持ち (おー！)
This burning feeling (Ohh!)
這い寄る！混沌！遣るらとほ！
Creeping! Chaos! Nyarlathotep!
オトナブルー
(作詞：新しい学校のリーダーズ　作曲：yonkey)
Otona Blue
(Lyrics: ATARASHII GAKKO!  Composition: yonkey)
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, don't you?
艶やかな この唇
These glossy lips
柔肌をそっと引き寄せる
Gently drawing in my soft skin
息を呑むほどに 甘い蜜
Honey so sweet it'll take your breath away
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, don't you?
二度見する この身体
This body that'll make you look twice
街ひとり歩けば 皆々様
When I walk the streets alone, everyone
視線が絡みつく
Has their eyes tangled around me
ねぇ、何を期待してるの？
Hey, what are you expecting?
そのうちじゃなく 今すぐがいいの
I don't want 'someday,' I want it right now
大人の恋に 焦がれて
Longing for an adult romance
見た目よりも残る あどけない
More than the looks, there's an innocent
心だけが 先走り
Heart that keeps running ahead
青い蕾のまま
Remaining as an unripe bud
オトナブルー
Otona Blue
わかってる 欲しいんでしょ
I know, you want it, don't you?
刺激する 私のすべて
Stimulating my everything
冷めた瞳まで魅了する
Fascinating even cold eyes
いつかは花になる アマリリス
An amaryllis that will bloom someday
せーの！
One, two!
言葉じゃなくて 心で繋がりたくて
Not through words, I want to connect through our hearts
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
I can't hide it with ordinary makeup
憧れだけ 夢を見る
Just longing, I see dreams
あなたの前でまた
Once again, in front of you
オトナブルー
Otona Blue
そのうちじゃなくて 今すぐがいいの
Not eventually, I want it right now
大人の恋に憧れて
Longing for an adult romance
見た目よりも残る あどけない
Innocence remains more than appearance
気持ちだけが 空回り
Only my feelings are spinning in circles
私を見つけて
Find me
せーの！
One, two!
言葉じゃなくて 心で繋がりたくて
Not through words, I want to connect through our hearts
ありきたりなメイクじゃ隠せない
I can't hide it with ordinary makeup
憧れだけ 夢を見る
Just longing, I see dreams
学ぶ恋路を
Learning the path of love
追いかけて
Chasing after it
また オトナ ブルー
Again, Otona Blue
未熟
Immature
無作法
Ill-mannered
然れど
But still
美しくあれ
Be beautiful
独り身にふさわしくない
Not suitable for a single person
これじゃきっと物足りない くらい語っとけばうまくいく
If I say it's not enough, things will surely go well
物、金、愛、事、もう自己顕示飽きた
Money, items, love, stuff... I'm tired of self-display
既視感 何がそんな不満なんだ
Déjà vu, what is so unsatisfying?
散々わがまま語っといて これ以上他に何がいる
After being so selfish, what more do you need?
そんなところも割と嫌いじゃない
I don't really hate that part of you either
もう聞き飽きたんだよ そのセリフ
I'm tired of hearing that line
中途半端だけは嫌
I hate half-heartedness
嫌
I hate it!
愛して どうして 言ってたって
Saying "Love me" and "Why?"
愛して どうして 言われたって
Even if told "Love me" and "Why?"
遊びだけなら簡単で
If it's just playing, it's easy
真剣勝負 ぐちゃぐちゃで
But a serious battle is a mess
思いもしない重い言葉
Heavy words I never thought of
何度使い古すのか
How many times will you reuse them?
どうせ期待してたんだ できレースでも
I was expecting it anyway, even if it's a fixed race
引用だらけのフレーズも
Even these phrases full of citations
かかと持ち上がる言葉 独り言にして
Keep the words that lift your heels as a monologue
空気を読んだ 雨降らないでよ
Read the room, please don't let it rain
まどろっこしい話はやめて
Stop with the tedious talk
必要最低限でいい 二文字以内でどうぞ
Keep it to the absolute minimum, two characters or less please
ほら その情は 前のめり？ もう 届かない
See, is that emotion leaning forward? It won't reach anymore
脆い 鎖 ほどけ
Loose the fragile chains
その頬を魅力的に
Make those cheeks charming
染めるでしょう？
It will color them, won't it?
メーデー 答えられないなら放っておいてくれ
Mayday, if you can't answer, just leave me alone
迷えるくらいならそっとしておいてくれ
If you're going to hesitate, just leave me be
肝心なとこは筒抜けで
The essential parts are leaking out
安心だけはさせられるような
Like you can only provide reassurance
甘い雨が降れば傘も差したくなるだろう
If sweet rain falls, you'll want to open an umbrella, right?
言葉 期待したままでよかった
I'm glad I kept expecting those words
目を瞑った かったるかった
I closed my eyes, it was tedious
大人ぶった 無くした
Acted mature, lost it
巻き戻せなかった
I couldn't rewind it
今更 止まないでよ
Don't stop now
ほっといて
Leave me alone
ペースト
Paste
デリート
Delete
その繰り返し
Repeating that
吸って 吐いた
Breathe in, breathe out
だから
Therefore
それでもいいからさ
Even so, it's fine
ここにいたいよ
I want to stay here
愛して どうして 言ってたって
Saying "Love me" and "Why?"
愛して どうして 言われたって
Even if told "Love me" and "Why?"
遊びだけなら簡単で
If it's just playing, it's easy
真剣勝負 支離滅裂で
A serious battle, incoherent
思いもしない重い嘘は
Heavy lies I never thought of
タブーにしなくちゃ
Must be made taboo
きっと期待してたんだ できレースでも
I'm sure I was expecting it, even if it's a fixed race
公式通りのフレーズも
Even the formulaic phrases
明るく振る舞って
Behaving brightly...
耳にして
Lend me your ear
空気を読んだ
I read the room
空晴れないでよ
Don't let the sky clear up
今日も雨
Rain again today
傘を閉じて
Closing the umbrella
濡れて帰ろうよ
Let's go home soaking wet
魂の色は
The color of the soul
何色ですか？
What color is it?
ANIMA / 作詞・作曲・編曲：毛蟹 (LIVE LAB.)
ANIMA / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Kegani (LIVE LAB.)
もう急かされたままで
Still being rushed
捨てるほど　逃げ出すほど
To the point of throwing it away, or running away
強くないよ　ほら
I'm not that strong, you see
もう一度　鼓動　高鳴る
Once again, my heart beats fast
何が正しいからなんて
Because of what is right or whatever
分からないけど
I don't know, but...
形のないものばかりが
Only things without form
大切になっていく
Are becoming precious
飾らない言葉だけが
Only words without decoration
強く結ばれてる
Are strongly bound
また躓いて　転がって
Tripping and rolling again
それでも挫けない
Even so, I won't be discouraged
魂の色は
The color of the soul
何色ですか？
What color is it?
ただ傷付いて　強がって
Just getting hurt and acting tough
それでも見つけたいよ
Even so, I want to find it
魂の形
The shape of the soul
確かめてるよ
I'm confirming it
暗い地の底で一人
Alone at the bottom of the dark earth
扉と鍵を探す
Searching for the door and the key
お伽話はほら
See, the fairy tale is...
泡のように全部消えて
All disappeared like bubbles
葛藤　残像だけ
Only conflict and afterimages
次のページへ
To the next page
伸びてく枝葉　分かれて
Branches extending and dividing
それぞれの道を行く
Going our separate ways
寂しい思い出だけが
Only lonely memories
強く根を張ってる
Are taking deep root
また貫いて　失って
Piercing and losing again
それでも挫けない
Even so, I won't be discouraged
心はどこに
Where is the heart?
いつまでもどこに
Where is it forever?
ただ残されて　抜け落ちて
Just left behind and falling out
それでも伝えたいよ
Even so, I want to convey it
魂の響きを
The resonance of the soul
魂の意思を
The will of the soul
ずっと... oh...
Forever... oh...
魂の色は
The color of the soul
何色ですか？
What color is it?
赤色ですか？
Is it red?
青色ですか？
Is it blue?
魂の色は
The color of the soul
何色ですか？
What color is it?
透明な過去に
To the transparent past
不透明な明日に
To the opaque tomorrow
生きる僕らは
We who live
何色ですか？
What color are we?
また躓いて　転がって
Tripping and rolling again
それでも挫けない
Even so, I won't be discouraged
魂の色は
What color...
何色ですか？
...is your soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって
I'm just getting hurt, acting tough
それでも見つけたいよ
But even so, I want to find it
魂の形
The shape of the soul
確かめてるよ
I'm making sure of it
ずっと
Forever
wow wow
ずっと
Forever
wow wow
ずっと
Forever
wow wow
ずっと
Forever
wow wow
1、2、3、4！
1, 2, 3, 4!
あんまり容赦しないで
Don't be so merciless
私だってケーキ公式なんていらない
I don't need a cake formula either
好きな解答がほしい
I want the answer I like
そう一気に毎日まみれて不安でしょう
Yeah, suddenly covered in daily life, it's unsettling, right?
そんな目できにしないで
Don't look at me like that
ハッピーエンドの小説みたいで素敵じゃない
Isn't it wonderful, like a happy-ending novel?
好きな解答がほしい
I want the answer I like
そう一気に毎日まみれて不安でしょう
Yeah, suddenly covered in daily life, it's unsettling, right?
好きな歌なら歌いたい
If it's a song I like, I want to sing it
欲しいものなら全部持ってると思ってたけど足りない
I thought I had everything I wanted, but it's not enough
私の想像超えて
Beyond my imagination
ああ叫べ 20時 間近のグリッター
Ah, shout! The glitter near 8 PM
気に入らないわ燃えるように
I don't like it, as if burning
競い合ってもクレイジー
Even if we compete, it's crazy
だってフリーキー I get just judge early
Because it's freaky, I get just judge early
そんなんじゃ私じゃわからない
I won't understand like that
行ったり来たりしないで
Don't go back and forth
簡単な事良い場所は忘れましょう
Forget the simple things and the good places
明日も少女でいたい裏腹に爪を
I want to be a girl tomorrow too, on the contrary, my nails...
邪魔してやまない
...won't stop getting in the way
中途半端でいられない
I can't be half-hearted
痛い事ならいつも持てると分かってるから待たない
I know I can always take the painful stuff, so I won't wait
かかってこいよベイビー
Come at me, baby
ああいてよファイア 空前絶後のムーヴ
Ah, stay there, fire! An unprecedented move
言い訳はしないで燃えるような
Don't make excuses, as if burning
私を見てよ好きに本当アメイジング
Look at me as you like, truly amazing
I change just standard ヒーロー
I change just standard hero
今のあなたはつまらない
You're boring right now
ああ叫べ 20時 間近のグリッター
Ah, shout! The glitter near 8 PM
気に入らないわ燃えるように
I don't like it, as if burning
競い合ってもクレイジー
Even if we compete, it's crazy
だってフリーキー I get just judge early
Because it's freaky, I get just judge early
いつまでもそこにいて
Stay there forever
叫べ 20時 確かに今に
Shout! 8 PM, surely now
気に入らないわ燃えるような
I don't like it, as if burning
瞳をしてる絶対絶度のフィーバー
Eyes that are... an absolute fever
こんな一大事
Such a critical moment
よそいきは捨てて迎えに来て
Throw away your formal appearance and come get me
Yeah! Oh!
どうだった？ねねのプロみたいな演奏は。Yeah!
How was it? Nene's professional-like performance. Yeah!
今日、見てみんな、これ。ねね専用のギターを用意してもらいました！
Look everyone, look at this. I had a Nene-exclusive guitar prepared!
Yeah! かっこいいでしょ？
Yeah! Isn't it cool?
もうすごいソロパートも弾けちゃうんだから。
I can even play an amazing solo part.
トゥルルルル... うぉー！
Trurururu... Whoa!
このかっこいいローアングルを用意してもらっちゃって。ちょっともう一回いいですか？
They even prepared this cool low angle for me. Can I do it one more time?
トゥルルルル... おぉー！
Trurururu... Ohhh!
さあ、みんなゲストパートはいかがだったでしょ...
Now, how did everyone like the guest part...
...いかがでしたでしょうかー！
...how did you like it!
いろんな、ね、ホロメンとあぁいうの歌ったらすごい良いんじゃないかなーとか
I thought it would be really nice to sing that kind of thing with various Holo members,
いろいろ考えながら選びましたー！
so I chose it while thinking about all sorts of things!
可愛かったでしょ？可愛かったでしょ？
It was cute, right? It was cute, right?
さあ、そして、ゲストの、あの、こう、サムネイルにいたけど、
Now, then, about the guests... they were in the thumbnail,
まだ出てきてないホロメンがいますよね？
but there are still some Holo members who haven't appeared yet, right?
いつもの人たちをお呼びしたいと思います。
I'd like to call out the usual crowd.
ちょっとね...
One moment...
あぁ！あ、ごめん。今行くね！
Ah! Oh, sorry. I'm coming now!
Hyper Jumpin'!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hyper Jumpin'
作詞・作曲・編曲：PandaBoY
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: PandaBoY
Hyper Jumpin'!
いくぞみんな！
Here we go, everyone!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hyper Jumpin'!
飛び出そう Come on baby
Let's jump out, Come on baby
輝いて ハートギュッと ぽっぴんわーるど
Shining bright, heart squeezed tight, Poppin' World
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' to the end of dreams
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
More and more, I want stimulation
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hyper Jumpin'!
せーの！
One, two!
Hyper Jumpin'!
一回きり はしゃぐほうが おトクでしょう
It's better to have fun while we can, once in a lifetime
限界突破 這い上がっていく テンション
Breaking through the limits, tension rising up
脳内は ラブ打ち返しまくる メンション
In my head, mentions of love hitting back over and over
波濤を乗りこなして進む ミッション
A mission proceeding by riding over the waves
このまま スピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the end of the journey
止まらない 気持ちは助走つけて
Gaining momentum with feelings that won't stop
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Let's go beyond dimensions, come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap around
灰になって ハイになるまで ダンシングオール
Dancing all until we turn to ash and get high
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sky
もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Wow wow wow
ドキドキしたい キミ キミ キミ アイ
I want to feel my heart pound, you, you, you, love
Wow wow wow
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
More and more, I want to jump higher
いくよ、せーの！
Here we go, one, two!
Hyper Jumpin'!
もう一回！いくよ、せーの！
One more time! Here we go, one, two!
Hyper Jumpin'!
斜めから 攻めて解決 クエスチョン
Solving questions by attacking from an angle
(ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！)
(Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!)
ネガティブ 置き去りにしてくれる 全勝
A total victory that leaves the negative behind
(きゅいーん！)
(Kyuin!)
流れる コメントと掛け合いで セッション
A session through interaction with flowing comments
(らみぃ！らみぃ！らみぃ！)
(Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!)
エイムを 鍛えて狙い撃つ フィクション
Fiction where you train your aim and shoot
ししろん！ Yeah!
Shishiron! Yeah!
リズムに乗んな 好きならもっともっと
Get on the rhythm, if you like it, more and more
邪魔するノイズは 打ち消せバンバンバン
Cancel out the interfering noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけ 安心安心して
Just want to play, rest assured
笑い飛ばして 蹴っ飛ばして 危機一髪 絶体絶命！
Laugh it off, kick it away, critical moment, desperate situation!
このまま 僕らは旅をして
Just like this, we continue our journey
辿り着く先に 何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the end of the journey
信じた 未来とリンクして
Link up with the future you believed in
次元を超えて行こう さあ
Let's go beyond dimensions, come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump across
灰になって ハイになるまで ダンシングオール
Dancing all until we turn to ash and get high
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea
もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer
はずきたいの
Want to get excited!
Wow wow wow...
ドキドキしたい
I want to feel my heart throb!
キミキミキミ アイ
You, you, you, love!
Wow wow wow...
もっともっと高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
ハイ！ハイ！
High! High!
ハイ！
High!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイパー！ハイパー！ジャンプ！ジャンプ！
Hyper! Hyper! Jump! Jump!
光る！光る！すごいでしょ！
It's glowing! Glowing! Amazing, right?
すげー！
Awesome!
はい！と、いうわけで、ねぽらぼのみんなに来てもらいましたー！
Yes! So, the NePoLaBo members have joined us!
じゃ、自己紹介しますね。
Well then, let's do our self-introductions.
いる？自己紹介。
Do we need introductions?
ホロライブ５期生、ねぽらぼの、可愛くてヒール担当、桃鈴ねねきゅん！
Hololive 5th gen, NePoLaBo's cute heel-in-charge, Momosuzu Nene-kyun!
あれ？エナジードリンク？
Huh? Energy drink?
みんなの心な、エナジードリンク！
For everyone's hearts, Energy Drink!
エナジードリンク！
Energy Drink!
チュ！桃鈴ねねです！
Chu! It's Momosuzu Nene!
さすがの可愛いメンバーは誰かな？
Who are the truly cute members?
みんなの心な、エナジードリンク！
For everyone's hearts, energy drink!
おまるポルカです！可愛い！
It's Omaru Polka! Cute!
心の、エナジードリンク！雪花ラミィです。
The heart's energy drink! I'm Yukihana Lamy.
ラブチュ！可愛い！
Love-chu! Cute!
誰かな？私か。
Who is it? Me.
心の、何だっけ？
The heart's, what was it?
エナジードリンク、プシュ！獅白ぼたんです！
Energy drink, pashu! It's Shishiro Botan!
みんな可愛いー！
Everyone is so cute!
このノリで行くの？ちょっとふざけすぎたね、なんか。
Are we going with this vibe? We messed around a bit too much.
本日も、お越しいただきましてありがとうございました！
Thank you very much for coming today!
めちゃ被っとる！
They're overlapping so much!
ハッシュタグ間違えないでね！
Don't get the hashtag wrong!
#桃鈴ねねの４年目 だからね、みんな。
It's #MomosuzuNeneNo4NenMe, okay everyone?
ししろ高所恐怖症なんで、そろそろ下ろしてもらってもいい？
Since Shishiro has a fear of heights, can we lower the stage soon?
下げてー！はい、下げて。
Lower it! Okay, lower it.
ちょっと先に始めてていいかな？
Is it okay if I start ahead of you?
主役は後から登場するから！
The main star always appears later!
マツケンサンバ II
Matsuken Samba II
桃鈴ねねさん、頑張って頑張ってきましたよ！４年目！
Momosuzu Nene has worked so hard! It's the 4th year!
マツケンサンバII
Matsuken Samba II
イエーイ！おめでとうございます！
Yay! Congratulations!
4周年、4年目おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on your 4th anniversary and 4th year!
ありがとうございます！ありがとう、皆さーん！
Thank you so much! Thank you, everyone!
いや、なんとおめでたい日にこんな曲を歌って
Well, on such an auspicious day, I'm going to sing this song
めでたくなっていこうと思っております！
to make things even more festive!
みんなポンポンでねねのことを目立たせてください！
Everyone, please use your pom-poms to make Nene stand out!
はい！それではねねさんのことを
Yes! Then we shall make Nene-san
目立たせようと思います！
stand out!
あー！見えない！
Ah! I can't see!
オラオラオラ！
Ora ora ora!
あ、始まる！そろそろ歌始まる！
Ah, it's starting! The song is about to start!
始まるよ！準備して！
It's starting! Get ready!
叩けボンゴ　響けサンバ
Beat the bongo, let the samba ring
踊れ南のカルナバル
Dance the southern carnival
誰も彼も　浮かれ騒ぎ
Everyone is in a festive mood
光る汗がはじけ飛ぶ
Sparkling sweat scatters about
ウー、ハッ！
Woo, hah!
熱い風に　体あずけ
Surrender your body to the hot wind
（ツイートしてほしい！）
(I want you to tweet!)
合図送れば　瞳キラリ
When I give the signal, your eyes sparkle
オレ！
Ole!
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
オレ！　オレ！
Ole! Ole!
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
踊れセニョリータ　眠りさえ忘れて
Dance, Señorita, forgetting even sleep
踊り明かそう　サンバ　ビバ　サンバ
Let's dance the night away, Samba Viva Samba
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
タッタッタ　オレ！
Ta-ta-ta, Ole!
あ、いいよいいよ、いいよ！このツイートしてなきゃいけない感じ！
Ah, nice, nice, nice! This feeling of having to tweet!
はけていく感じめちゃ良かったわ！
The way you guys cleared out was great!
今しばらくツイートしましたよ。
I was tweeting for a while just now.
ちょっとねねここツイートして良さそう。大事なところ！
Wait, I think I should tweet here. This is important!
ねね、ソロパート？ソロパートなの？
Nene, solo part? Is it a solo part?
ずっとオンステージだから！あまり動かないから無理しないでね。
I'm always on stage! I won't move much, so don't overdo it.
あ、なんかこれ動画寄ってっちゃう、ああー！
Ah, the camera is zooming in, aaah!
輝けねね！もっと出てくるよ！
Shine, Nene! More is coming!
オレ！ハート作るよ！
Ole! Let's make a heart!
まだ間奏だったー！
It was still the instrumental break!
間奏長すぎだろ、こっち！まだだよ、まだね。
This instrumental is too long! Not yet, not yet.
ねねち！ねねち！もっとコメント盛り上げて！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Hype up the comments more!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
タッタッタ！
Ta-ta-ta!
あ、いいよいいよ！お祝い歌始まります！
Ah, nice, nice! The celebratory song is starting!
叩けボンゴ　響けサンバ
Beat the bongo, let the samba ring
踊れ南のカルナバル
Dance the southern carnival
夢のようね　ときめきは
It's like a dream, this excitement
真珠色の　愛の夜
A pearl-colored night of love
焼けた素肌　肩を抱いて
Embracing shoulders and sun-kissed skin
愛をささやき　踊れば
Whispering love as we dance
白い渚に　恋も輝き
Love also shines on the white shore
風に誘われ　歌いだす
Invited by the wind, I start to sing
オレ！オレ！
Ole! Ole!
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
オレ！オレ！
Ole! Ole!
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
踊れセニョリータ　眠りさえ忘れて
Dance, Señorita, forgetting even sleep
踊り明かそう　サンバ　ビバ　サンバ
Let's dance the night away, Samba Viva Samba
マツケンサンバ　オレ！
Matsuken Samba Ole!
行くよ！オレ！
Here we go! Ole!
ありがとうございましたー！おめでとうー！
Thank you very much! Congratulations!
ありがとうー！あーかゆい！かゆい！
Thank you! Ah, it's itchy! Itchy!
おめでとー！あー！
Congratulations! Aaah!
見て、これ。ねねの花火。ありがとう、ねねの花火。
Look at this. Nene's fireworks. Thank you, Nene's fireworks.
ラミィのお目目にも花火が。何言ってんの？
There are fireworks in Lamy's eyes too. What are you saying?
どうした？大丈夫か？というわけで皆さん、
What's wrong? Are you okay? Anyway, everyone,
お水の方は大丈夫ですかね？
are you okay with water (staying hydrated)?
オレ！大丈夫！
Ole! I'm okay!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて。
Calm down, calm down.
というわけで皆さんちょっとあの、
Anyway, everyone, I'd like to ask you to
グッズ紹介お付き合いいただいてもよろしいでしょうか。お願いします！
join me for a short merchandise introduction. Please!
さあここで今回のねね4周年目に向けたオリジナルグッズ紹介です！
Now, it's time to introduce the original goods for Nene's 4th anniversary!
こちら、ドーン！3Dライブ開催記念！
Here they are, bam! 3D Live Commemorative Goods!
3Dライブ開催記念
3D Live Commemorative
3Dライブ開催記念グッズ、イエーイ！
3D Live Commemorative Goods, yay!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな、このイラストは、今回お写真なんと...
Everyone, for this illustration and photo...
西沢5㍉先生です！
it's Nishizawa 5mm-sensei!
西沢5㍉先生！
Nishizawa 5mm-sensei!
はい、というわけで最初は、こちら！ドン！
Alright, so first off, here's this! Boom!
ねっ子ぬいぐるみ ver.2023（にんじん）！
Nekko Plushie ver.2023 (Carrot)!
来ました！来ました！
It's here! It's here!
見たことある。
I've seen this before.
どこが違うんですか？
What's the difference?
はい、ねっ子も成長いたしまして、なんと推しの前で...
Yes, the Nekko has grown, and surprisingly, in front of their oshi...
...よだれを垂らすようになったということでーす！
...they've started to drool!
なるほどー。
I see.
はい次！
Okay, next!
え？あれ？
Eh? Wait?
これは、第一世代のにんじんねっこの、だいこんバージョン！
This is the Radish version of the first-generation Carrot Nekko!
第一世代なんだ！
So it's first generation!
そう、まだよだれ垂らしてない。無垢な。
Yeah, it's not drooling yet. Innocent.
次、第二世代、PROとか出てくる？
Next, second generation, will there be a PRO version?
色違いね、欲しいな。PRO MAXとか出てくるかも。
Color variations, I want them. Maybe a PRO MAX will come out.
大きくなっちゃうかも。いっぱい買って！
It might get bigger. Buy lots of them!
そして次、ちょっとごめんね、おまるのいいなーと思って真似しました！ドン！
And next, sorry, I thought Omaru's was nice, so I copied it! Boom!
え、何真似したの？あー！ハッピ！
Eh, what did you copy? Ah! Happi!
ハッピだー！イエーイ！
It's a Happi! Yay!
これなんですか？
What is this?
はい、ねねの推しハッピになります！
Yes, this is Nene's Oshi Happi!
イエーイ！
Yay!
じゃあこれさ、私とラミィちゃん出てないじゃん、ハッピに。
Then, Lamy and I aren't on the Happi, are we?
あ、そうだ、これは強制的に次出せってこと？
Oh, right, so we're forced to be in the next one?
ねねコラボハッピ、熱いよこれ。
Nene collab Happi, that's hot.
熱いね、作らないといけないね。
Hot indeed, we have to make it.
そういうこと。今回表と裏でちょっとずつ表情が違うので...
That's right. This time the expressions are slightly different on the front and back...
...よかったらじっくりあとで見てみてください！
...so please take a good look later!
そして、全部揃えてくれた方のセットはこちら！
And here's the set for those who get everything!
フルセットだー！ドン！
Full set! Boom!
あー、ボイス！ボイスだ！ボイスも出ます！
Ah, voice! It's a voice! A voice will also be released!
どんなボイスなんですか？
What kind of voice is it?
はい、ねっ子をお友達と捉えまして、通話のボイスが出ます！
Yes, treating Nekko as a friend, there's a voice call!
なんと、ハズバンドから降格です！
What, demoted from husband!
え、ちょっとまだね、これからねねの深いファンになっちゃうかな？みたいな人。
Wait, it's for people like, "I might become a deep fan of Nene from now on."
まずはお友達から始めましょう。
Let's start as friends first.
そして、全部揃えてくれた方、こちら！ドン！
And for those who get everything, here! Boom!
チェキ風のブロマイドカードと特典のボイスが付きます！
It comes with a cheki-style bromide card and a bonus voice!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
詳細はこちら、ドン！
Details are here, boom!
はい、今回直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード、表情差分のねねが...
Yes, this time, a handwritten-signed cheki-style bromide card, with different facial expressions for Nene...
まさかこれは全員に？
Wait, is this for everyone?
あ、全員に書きます！
Ah, I'll write it for everyone!
おおー！
Whoa!
そして、通話の、あ、じゃないじゃない、特典のボイスが...
And the call, oh, no no, the bonus voice...
...ちょっとさっきのとこから進展がありまして...
...has some progress from the previous one...
...二人で寝落ち通話なんてしちゃう、あら、あら。
...we'll do a sleep-over call together, oh my, oh my.
だいぶ進展しちゃって！
Quite some progress!
ええ、夜に二人で「眠れないよー」みたいなこと言ってるボイスが...
Yeah, a voice where we're saying "I can't sleep" together at night...
...眠れないよー、で気が付いたら寝ちゃってるやつですねー！
..."I can't sleep", and then before you know it, you're asleep!
いいですねー！
That's nice!
そういうの聞きながら寝る派だ！
I'm the type to sleep while listening to that!
えー、そして、えー、次が最後の曲になるんですけど、みんな。
Uh, and, uh, next will be the last song, everyone.
お、なんですか？
Oh, what is it?
ねね最近、あの、新曲出したんですよ。
Nene recently, um, released a new song.
あ、ギラファですね！
Ah, Giraffa!
ギラギラギラファ！
Gira Gira Giraffa!
ギラギラギラファなの、ギラファなの、ギラファにしようかな。
Gira Gira Giraffa, it's Giraffa, maybe I'll go with Giraffa.
ギラファ！ギラファ！
Giraffa! Giraffa!
はい、そしてそのMVがもう枠立ってるんですけど...
Yes, and the MV for it has already been scheduled...
...22時15分から公開になります！
...it will be released at 22:15!
おー、楽しみだー！
Oh, looking forward to it!
そしてその前に！
And before that!
えー、振り付けがある、お、振り付けがあるので...
Uh, there's choreography, oh, since there's choreography...
...まずはそちらを初披露してから、みんなの元にMVお届けしたいと思ってて。
...I want to perform it for the first time first, and then deliver the MV to everyone.
でもこのギラファのMVの後にも、もう一曲ちょっと匂わせあるので楽しみにしてください！
But after this Giraffa MV, there's a little tease for another song, so please look forward to it!
匂わせだ！匂わせ大好き！
A tease! We love teases!
えー、じゃあみなさん、ありがとうございました！
Uh, then, everyone, thank you very much!
お邪魔しましたー！
Sorry for bothering you! / We're leaving now!
ありがとうございました、頑張ります。
Thank you very much, I'll do my best.
頑張って！お邪魔しましたー、またなー！
Do your best! Bye-bye, see ya later!
はー、あ、まだいましたおまるんが。
Hah, ah, Omarun was still here.
はい、というわけで、ねねもお着替えして...
Okay, so Nene will also change clothes...
...ギラギラファンミーティング、みんなと一緒に歌って踊っていきたいと思います！
...and I'd like to sing and dance "Gira Gira Fan Meeting" with everyone!
ほな、お着替え！
Now, let's change!
ハッピーギラファ！
Happy Giraffa!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Gira Gira Fan Meeting!
さあ、ツノとアゴ長く伸ばして、思いっきり楽しんじゃおうね！
Come on, stretch those horns and jaws long, and let's have a blast!
それじゃあいくよ！
Alright, here we go!
アピをかけろ、ビバ！ギラファ！
Show off, Viva! Giraffa!
カブ・クワ！ギラギラ最高潮だぜ！
Kabu-Kuwa! Gira Gira at its peak!
カブ・クワ！アサマ・カブ・クワ、イエーイ！
Kabu-Kuwa! Asama Kabu-Kuwa, yay!
カブ・クワ！クリクリおめめラブ
Kabu-Kuwa! Twinkling eyes love
カブ・クワ！アサマ・カブ・クワ、イエーイ！
Kabu-Kuwa! Asama Kabu-Kuwa, yay!
愛のナツはムチャムチャ飛んで
The summer of love is flying wildly
シュビドゥバメロメロ
Shu-bi-du-ba head over heels
みんな集まれゾロゾロバン
Everyone gather in a swarm, bang
チュ、チュ、バヤバヤパパヤパ！
Chu, chu, baya baya pa pa ya pa!
ギラ ギラ ギラ ギラ...
Gira Gira Gira Gira...
目覚めたなら元気に おはよう
If you wake up, say an energetic "Good morning"
Let's Go カブクワパラダイス
Let's Go Kabu-Kuwa Paradise
オシャレなんてそっちのけ 出かけよう
Forget about being fashionable, let's head out
行ってきまーす！
I'm heading out!
エレファス コーカサス ヘラクレス ノコギリ タランドゥス
Elephas, Caucasus, Hercules, Prosopocoilus, Tarandus
Ha!! さあ ファンミーティングが始まる Uh Wow!!
Ha!! Now, the fan meeting begins! Uh Wow!!
出ておいでよ
Come on out!
ギラファ！
Giraffa!
カブクワ！
Kabu-Kuwa!
ギラギラ最大級
The ultimate sparkle
カブクワ！ Prrrrrr Howl!
Kabu-Kuwa! Prrrrrr Howl!
カブクワ！
Kabu-Kuwa!
テカテカツヤツヤの
Big, shiny, and glossy
Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
パツパツ！
Patsu-patsu!
ムーチャムーチャ可愛い！
So, so cute!
Full!
ツヤツヤ！ 敵をペロペロ！
Shiny! Lick the enemies!
みんな！
Everyone!
集まれゾロゾロ
Gather around in droves
パンチュッパイヤッパイヤッパッパッ
Pan-chu-pai-ya-pai-ya-pa-pa
薄力粉と砂糖と焼酎たっぷり袋に加えましょう
Add flour, sugar, and shochu into the bag
両手でクワッとひと掴み さあ 揉んで 揉んで 揉んで 揉んで
Grab a handful with a "Kuwa"! Now knead, knead, knead, knead
発酵した愛の樹液 I want you 君専用ジュエリー
The fermented sap of love! I want you, your own jewelry
カブクワ欲しけりゃ 塗りたくれ！
If you want Kabu-Kuwa, slather it on!
さあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあさあ
Sa-sa-sa-sa...
塗ったら揺らせ
Once you slather it on, shake it
ヨイショヨイショ... 足腰叩け
Yoisho, yoisho... Beat your legs and hips
バンバンバンバン...
Bang, bang...
踊らなきゃ 踊れ！ Yeah!!
You gotta dance, dance! Yeah!!
すごーい！みんなのおかげで、こんなにたくさんのカブクワたちが集まってくれたよ！
Amazing! Thanks to everyone, so many Kabu-Kuwas have gathered!
自分に拍手！
Applause for yourselves!
そして自然に拍手！
And applause for nature!
アヌビスレギウスマルマルス
Anubis regius, Mesotopus tarandus
ニジイロクランディス Ha!!
Rainbow beetle, Lucanus chinensis Ha!!
みんなそれぞれ愛してるけど
I love everyone in their own way, but...
やっぱり君が好き 誰だ？
after all, I love you the most. Who is it?
ギラファ ギラファ ギラファ ギラファ
Giraffa, Giraffa, Giraffa, Giraffa
強くてかっこいい
Strong and cool
キラキラファンタスティックなノコギリバ
Sparkling fantastic stag beetle...
Uh Wow! 宝物だよ
Uh Wow! It's a treasure
ギラファ！ カブクワ！
Giraffa! Kabu-Kuwa!
ギラキラ最高だぜ カブクワ！
Sparkle is the best! Kabu-Kuwa!
Prrrrrr Howl!
カブクワ！ クリクリおめめラブ
Kabu-Kuwa! Love those big round eyes
カブクワ！ Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
Kabu-Kuwa! Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
Kabu-Kuwa...
パンチュッパイヤッパイヤッパッパッ
Pan-chu-pai-ya-pai-ya-pa-pa
みんな今日は見てくれてありがとねー！
Everyone, thank you for watching today!
このあともう少しあるよ！
There's a little bit more coming up after this!
ほっぴっぽーほっぴっぽー...
Hoppi-ppo-, hoppi-ppo-...
はぴー！！
Happy!!
はっぴっぽー
Hoppi-ppo-
さあ 飲みな お前好きだろ 野菜ジュース
Come on, drink up. You like vegetable juice, right?
私が決めた 今決めた
I've decided. Just now.
だから飲みな 私の野菜ジュース
So drink up, my vegetable juice
価格は200円
Price is 200 yen
どっせー どっせー そいや そいや
Dossee, dossee, soiya, soiya
まろやか野菜ジュース
Mellow vegetable juice
ふわふわ野菜ジュース
Fluffy vegetable juice
一番オススメなのは
The one I recommend most is
緑のジュース
The green juice
ほっぴっぽー ほっぴっぽー
Hoppi-ppo-, hoppi-ppo-
ベジタブルな...
Vegetable-like...
ポップ! ステップ! プット! オン!
Pop! Step! Put! On!
生命あふれた
Overflowing with life
ポップ! ステップ! プット! オン!
Pop! Step! Put! On!
あなたも今
You too, now
ポップ! ステップ! プット! オン!
Pop! Step! Put! On!
野菜ジュースが 好きになる
You'll come to like vegetable juice
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
「歌ってみた」先行配信中なので 聴いてください！
The cover song is out for early distribution, so please listen to it!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
ノメノメノメノメ...
Drink, drink, drink, drink...